export const BROWSERS_AND_HOW_THEY_WORK = [
    {
        questionNumber: 1,
        question: "What is the User Interface (UI) for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 2,
        question: "What is the UI Backend for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 3,
        question: "What is Data Persistence for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 4,
        question: "What is Networking for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Handles any network requests",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 5,
        question: "What is the Javascript Interpreter for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Interprets the Javascript",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 6,
        question: "What is the Rendering Engine for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 7,
        question: "What is the Browser Engine for?",
        options: [
            "Stores data e.g. cookies and local storage",
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
            "Provides visible browser elements e.g. refresh button",
            "Shows the actual \"website\"",
            "Handles any network requests",
            "Interprets the Javascript",
            "Uses the user interface methods of the underlying operating system. It is mainly used for drawing basic widgets (windows and combo boxes)"
        ],
        answer:
            "Handles actions from UI e.g. refreshing the page",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 8,
        question: "True or False - When receiving the HTML, we parse the HTML into a DOM tree (an object representation of the HTML).",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        answer:
            "True",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 9,
        question: "True or False - When receiving the CSS from a website, we also parse the CSS into a DOM tree.",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False. Stylesheets are parsed by a CSS parser and create the Style Rules."
        ],
        answer:
            "False. Stylesheets are parsed by a CSS parser and create the Style Rules.",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 10,
        question: "I create rectangular areas to represent the combined DOM tree and Style Rules (only the visible elements). What am I?",
        options: [
            "Layout",
            "Render Tree",
            "Painting",
            "Display"
        ],
        answer:
            "Render Tree",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 11,
        question: "I position and size all these rectangular blocks. I use a 'dirty bit system'. Every element has a dirty bit that's set to false. If it needs updating it's set to true. What am I?",
        options: [
            "Layout",
            "Render Tree",
            "Painting",
            "Display"
        ],
        answer:
            "Layout",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
    {
        questionNumber: 12,
        question: "I go through each element and display what you actually want to display. What am I?",
        options: [
            "Layout",
            "Render Tree",
            "Painting",
            "Display"
        ],
        answer:
            "Painting",
        minSelection: 1,
        maxSelection: 1,
    },
]